DAN KLEIN: So far, we have backtracking
search and we'd like to
make it better.
And here, there are some general purpose
ideas that apply to any CSP
that will give us huge gains in speed.
One idea is ordering.
So, which variable should
be assigned next?
As we'll see, there is better orderings
and worse orderings.
Similarly, for values, which order
should we try them in?
Some values are going to work
out, some values aren't.
Maybe we should be smart about
the order we try them.
Another big class of ways of
speeding up backtracking is
what's called filtering.
Is there some way to detect an
inevitable failure early so we don't
have to go through a whole bunch
of assigning to discover it?
And then finally, we're going to look at
structure methods where we look at
the constraint graph and exploit its
structure in some way in order to get
a better algorithm.